adsenseexperts.com 2014-02-12

# Privacy Policy for the use of AdSenseExperts.com

This is a privacy policy for AdSenseExperts.com. AdSenseExperts.com respects your privacy.  
Below is an outline of the information that AdSenseExperts.com gathers, how it’s used, and how you can “opt-out”

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy.  
You may contact us by email at the: [info@adsenseexperts.com](mailto:info@AdSenseexperts.com)

**Site Visits:**

Whenever you request a page through your browser, navigation and clickstream data such as:

  * your IP address,
  * browser and version,
  * operating system,
  * date and time and
  * the site from which you came

are stored in a log file and/or database. Any search terms that you enter into the AdSenseExperts.com Site Search are also logged.  
This information cannot be used to identify specific individuals, and is only used for:

  * Website and system administration,  

  * research and development,  

  * anonymous user analysis, and  

  * to provide accurate statistics to advertisers in the form of aggregated data.

This information is kept on a secure dedicated server hosted by [Hetzner Online AG](http://www.hetzner.de/).

The email addresses collected from subscriptions to the AdSenseExperts.com forum or newsletters are not sold,  
or disclosed to any third parties. These addresses will only be used by our business to send out AdSenseExperts.com   
communications (for example, the AdSenseExperts.com newsletters). You will not receive any mailings you did not request.  
You can remove yourself from our list at any time by visiting http://www.adsenseexperts.com/profile.php?do=editoptions

When a contest/sweepstakes/survey is run on this site you may be asked to supply some personally identifying information  
like your name, email address and/or phone number. This information will only be used to notify winners of the   
contest/sweepstakes. Non-identifying information may be analyzed, aggregated and presented to third-parties to provide   
an overview of the demographics of our Network´s visitors.

When a survey appears on the AdSenseExperts.com Network, information is collected, compiled and analyzed   
on an aggregated basis. AdSenseExperts.com may share this aggregated data with advertisers or business partners.

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Website.   
A cookie is an element of data that a Website can send to your browser, and which your browser may then store on your system.   
You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Doing this will allow you to decide on a case-by-case basis   
whether to accept cookies or not.

Cookies on this site are used by ourselves, our ad management system, by Google Analytics and occasionally by advertisers   
who use 3rd party ad serving solutions. 

Cookies are used for:

  * ad tracking,
  * customization of content (i.e. not repeating pop-up windows),
  * storing login information, and
  * statistical site-traffic analysis.

The information collected during the registration process for the AdSenseExperts.com Community is used to:
  * contact members,
  * customize content based upon user preferences,
  * display member status, and
  * display the date of a member´s last visit.

Information collected in this process can also be used to prevent banned users from re-registering under a different username.   
The email address will only be seen by administrators. Cookies may be sent to your browser to enable automatic log-ins   
upon further visits, as well as for content customization.

Any postings in our Forums should be considered public knowledge and will be accessible by search engine spiders.   
This includes any information you provode in the "profile" associated with any accounts you have at AdSenseExperts.com.   
AdSenseExperts.com will not retroactively edit your username, profile or posted messages.

Any messages sent through AdSenseExperts.com's servers, including person-to-person communcations, are unencrypted   
and may be accessed by AdSenseExperts.com Employees or Contractors.

AdSenseExperts.com complies with all law enforcement agency requests for information.

Any data collected will be used by ourselves and our agents. AdSenseExperts.com hereby reserves the right   
to transfer any data collected in the event of an acquisition, full or partial, of the company or its assets.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policies, or require assistance in opting out of our email lists,   
please contact info@adsenseExperts.com

**Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).   
Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze   
how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address)   
will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose   
of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services   
relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do   
so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with   
any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser,   
however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website,  
you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**Facebook "Like"-, Google “+1”- and Twitter button**

Our website uses social plugins ("Plugins"), like the Facebook "Like"-, Google “+1” and the “Twitter”-button from the social networks Facebook, Google Plus and Twitter. The plugins are marked with a Facebook logo, a “+1” (for Google +1) or the Twitter logo. When you visit a webpage of our website which contains such a plugin, your browser connects directly with the Facebook, Google and Twitter servers. The contents of the plugin is sent to your browser from Facebook, Google or Twitter directly and is incorporated into the website. By integrating the Facebook, Google +1 and Twitter plugin, Facebook, Google and Twitter receive the information that you requested the corresponding page on our website. If you are logged in into your Facebook, Google Plus and/or Twitter account, Facebook, Google and/or Twitter can associate your visit on our website with your Facebook, Google Plus and/or Twitter account. When you interact with the plugins, for example, the “Like”-, "+1"- or “Tweet”-button, the corresponding information is sent directly from your browser and stored on Facebook, Google Plus or Twitter. The purpose and scope of data collection and further processing, the use of this data by Facebook, Google and Twitter as well as your rights and preference settings for the protection of your privacy can be found in the [Data Use Policy from Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php), [the Google +1 Button Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/+/policy/+1button.html) and Twitter Privacy Policy. If you do not want that Facebook, Google or Twitter collects data on our website about you, you must log out on Facebook, Google and Twitter before you visit our website.

Last modified: 31/10/2010
